Fox Movietone Newsreel Collection - World War II Paper Records
Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division, Library of Congress
Fox Movietone newsreel collection - World War II paper records 1922-1946 (bulk 1941-1946)
MBRSMI007001
Twentieth Century-Fox Film Corporation
14,000 items 37 containers plus 7 oversize 16 linear feet
Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Cameramen’s dope sheets (detailed notes of stories filmed), continuity sheets (synopses of newsreels distributed to theaters), and turnovers (one sentence descriptions of each story filmed) from this major pioneer in the newsreel industry. Collection also contains other paper materials including telegrams, speeches, photographs, programs, and memoranda that provide details of the newsreels created by Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation. Although the entire Fox Movietone newsreel collection spans 1916-1963, these materials document the World War II period.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically therein.
People
Attlee, C. R. (Clement Richard), 1883-1967.; Chiang, Kai-shek, 1887-1975.; Chiang, May-ling Soong, 1897-2003.; Churchill, Winston, 1874-1965.; Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1890-1969.; Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain, 1926-; Gaulle, Charles de, 1890-1970.; Halsey, William Frederick, 1882-1959.; Hirohito, Emperor of Japan, 1901-1989.; Hitler, Adolf, 1889-1945.; Hull, Cordell, 1871-1955.; Laval, Pierre, 1883-1945.; Lehr, Lew, 1895-1950.; MacArthur, Douglas, 1880-1964.; Marshall, George C. (George Catlett), 1880-1959.; Molotov, Vyacheslav Mikhaylovich, 1890-1986.; Montgomery of Alamein, Bernard Law Montgomery, Viscount, 1887-1976.; Mussolini, Benito, 1883-1945.; Nimitz, Chester W. (Chester William), 1885-1966.; Patton, George S. (George Smith), 1885-1945.; Pétain, Philippe, 1856-1951.; Rommel, Erwin, 1891-1944.; Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945.; Spellman, Francis, 1889-1967.; Stalin, Joseph, 1879-1953.; Stettinius, Edward R. (Edward Reilly), 1900-1949.; Stimson, Henry L. (Henry Lewis), 1867-1950.; Thomas, Lowell, 1892-1981.; Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972.; Wainwright, Jonathan Mayhew, 1883-1953.; Windsor, Edward, Duke of, 1894-1972.; Windsor, Wallis Warfield, Duchess of, 1896-1986.
Organizations
Allied Forces.; Catholic Church--Clergy--Appointment, call, and election.; Conversations on International Organization (1944: Washington, D.C.); Dumbarton Oaks Conference (1944); Great Britain. Royal Air Force.; Malta Conference (1945); Potsdam Conference (1945); Twentieth Century-Fox Film Corporation.; United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration.; United Nations--History.; United Nations. Charter.; United States. Army Air Forces.; United States. Army.; United States. Army. Women's Army Auxiliary Corps.; United States. Army. Women's Army Corps.; United States. Coast Guard.; United States. Marine Corps.; United States. Navy.; World Series (Baseball); Yalta Conference (1945)
Subjects
Aachen, Battle of, Aachen, Germany, 1944.; Atomic bomb.; Baseball--United States.; Bombing, Aerial--Japan.; Cardinals.; College sports--United States.; Concentration camps.; Dieppe Raid, 1942.; Fashion--History--20th century.; Football--United States.; Heroes.; Holocaust, Jewish (1939-1945); Hosiery industry--United States.; Iwo Jima, Battle of, Japan, 1945.; Newsreels.; Nuremberg Trial of Major German War Criminals, Nuremberg, Germany, 1945-1946.; Orphans--Europe.; Peace treaties.; Pearl Harbor (Hawaii), Attack on, 1941.; Prisoners of war.; Rationing.; Reconstruction (1939-1951); Refugees.; Savings bonds--United States.; Shipbuilding--United States.; Trials (Crimes against humanity); War films.; Warships--United States.; World War, 1939-1945--Aerial operations, American.; World War, 1939-1945--Aerial operations, British.; World War, 1939-1945--Campaigns--Germany.; World War, 1939-1945--Campaigns--Japan--Okinawa Island.; World War, 1939-1945--Campaigns--Japan.; World War, 1939-1945--Campaigns--Philippines.; World War, 1939-1945--Collaborationists.; World War, 1939-1945--Engineering and construction.; World War, 1939-1945--Occupied territories.; World War, 1939-1945--Participation, Female.; World War, 1939-1945--Social aspects--United States.; World War, 1939-1945--War work--United States.; World War, 1939-1945.
Places
Hiroshima-shi (Japan)--History--Bombardment, 1945.; Japan--History--Allied occupation, 1945-1952.; United States--Armed Forces--Drill and tactics.; United States--Social life and customs--1918-1945.
Occupations
Generals--United States.; Presidents--United States.
Administrative Information
Provenance
Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation deposited the collection at the Library of Congress in 2003.
Access
Fox Movietone newsreel collection - World War II paper records is housed within the Moving Image Section of the Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division of the Library of Congress. For further information and for access to the collection, contact the Reference Desk in the Moving Image Reference Center at (202) 707-8572.
Related Materials
The Newsfilm Library at the University of South Carolina in Columbia owns an estimated 11 million feet of Fox News film and paper materials associated with this collection. To access, see:
Records of the Movietone News [MVTN]
.
Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation at Fox News, New York, NY retains portions of this collection.
Newsreels described by the paper documentation of this collection can be found in the Moving Image Section of this Division. Contact the
Motion Picture & Television Reading Room
for more information.
Other moving image collections can also be requested through the
Motion Picture & Television Reading Room
. See:
French Collection
German Collection
Italian Collection
Japanese Collection
Russian Collection
British Information Services Collection
U.S. Government Films Collection
AFI/Cromwell (Victor & Walter) Collection
Armed Forces Radio & Television Service
The Recorded Sound Section of this Division holds related recorded sound collections. To begin a search, consult the World War II finding aid and the Recorded Sound Catalog Supplement through the
Recorded Sound Reference Center
. See also these individual collections:
NBC Radio Collection
Mary Margaret McBride Collection
Raymond Swing Collection
Marine Corps Combat Recordings
Russian Collection
John Toland Collection
Armed Forces Radio and Television Service Collection or AFRTS Collection
David P. Boder Audio Materials
OWI Collection or OWI Radio Collection
Audioscriptions Collection
American Broadcasting Station in Europe Collection or ABSIE Collection
Separated Nuremberg Trial Recordings from the Robert H. Jackson Papers
Captured German Recordings
NSDAP [Nationalsozialistische Deutsche Arbeiterpartei]
V Disc Collection
Historical Note
Date Event
1919 Fox News first silent theatrical release
1926 Fox News becomes Fox-Movietone News
1927 Sound introduced to silent newsreels
1930-1934 Fox-Movietone News shares film equipment and footage with Hearst Corporation
1935 Fox-Movietone News becomes 20th Century-Fox Movietone News
1952-1963 Association with United Press International creates worldwide television news service
1963 Final newsreel theatrical presentation
Scope and Content Note
Although the title of this portion of the Fox Movietone newsreel collection designates World War II records, it is noted that other stories are reported, including sports, fashion, news of the nation, weather disasters, and entertainment. While the war dominated the news reported during this period, the news on the American home front is also well documented in this collection. The finding aid created in 2007 describes the materials in the Fox Movietone newsreel collection documenting the US involvement in World War II, roughly 1941-1946. The entire collection includes materials from 1916-1963. It is anticipated that the remainder of the materials will be processed and added to this finding aid in the future.
The majority of the materials in this collection were created at a time when the United States had just undergone a surprise attack on Pearl Harbor. The documents were originally created for a limited, private readership, and emotions were not as camouflaged as they might be when considered by current standards. Some of the language found in the collection could be construed as politically incorrect at the time this finding aid was created. No attempt to censor these materials has been made. By making this collection available, it is hoped that researchers will gain a greater insight into the complexities of this period in American history.
As stated in the Related Materials and Processing History portions of this finding aid, the Newsfilm Library at the University of South Carolina owns materials associated with this collection. Specifically, the dope sheets from approximately September 1942 to January 1945 are housed at the Newsfilm Library. However, the continuity sheets and turnovers, which provide synopses of the stories, can be found at the Library of Congress. It is anticipated that all of the materials in these two repositories will be digitized in the future for Internet access to researchers.
This collection is organized into three series: Dope Sheets, Continuity Sheets, and Turnovers. The Continuity Sheets Series is organized into two subseries: Lavenders and Summaries.
The first series, Dope Sheets, 1922-1946, undated, contains the most detail for all stories filmed. They can include the cameraman's name, his notations of story topic, location where the story was shot, dates surrounding the filming, principal personalities in the story, shot-by-shot descriptions of the story, environmental conditions during filming, length of footage shot, and other details germane to the story and its filming. Ancillary materials may also be found within each story and can include photographs, telegrams, news clippings, speeches, biographies of personalities, and event programs. The Dope sheets are arranged numerically, with each film assigned a unique story number. Prominent figures are frequently featured in these materials. Please see the Selected Search Terms section of this finding aid for a detailed listing.
The second series, Continuity Sheets, span the dates 1941-1946, and are organized into two subseries: Lavenders and Summaries. Continuity Sheets record the stories that made up the newsreels distributed to theaters, and the dates of distribution. They do not include all stories filmed. They provide synopses of the details included in the Dope Sheets. What differentiates the two subseries is: Lavenders supply the individual story numbers that create the newsreel; Summaries supply the footage length of each finished newsreel segment. Continuity Sheets are arranged in chronological order, with a volume and release number assigned to each distribution date.
The third series, Turnovers, 1940-1946, is organized by year, then date distributed to theaters, with a volume and release number assigned to each distribution date. For each distribution sheet, a list of story numbers, a one-sentence description for each story number, and the cameraman or creator for each story is listed. In addition, each turnover sheet separates the stories that were included in newsreels from those that were not. Scanning this series for specific stories is a good place for researchers to begin, if one knows the approximate date of the story sought.
Collection Arrangement
The collection is arranged in 3 series:
Dope Sheets
Continuity Sheets
Turnovers
http://lccn.loc.gov/2007641041
Container List
- Dope Sheets, 1922-1946, undated (Box 237-254, OV1-OV7)
  Cameramen's details of films shot, including dates, locations, subjects, length of footage. Story numbers may contain ancillary materials including photographs, news clippings, speeches, event programs, telegrams, and biographies.
  Arranged numerically by story number assigned to each film created. Separated oversize materials are listed at the end of this series.
  - 44-600 to 44-650, 1941 August-September (Box-folder 237/1)
  - 44-651 to 44-699, 1930s-1941 September, 44-698 contains dope sheets from the 1930s, stamped A3309-A3314. (Box-folder 237/2)
  - 44-700 to 44-750, 1941 July-September (Box-folder 237/3)
  - 44-751 to 44-799, 1941 September-October (Box-folder 237/4)
  - 44-800 to 44-843, 1941 August-October (Box-folder 237/5)
  - 44-844 to 44-899, 1941 September-October (Box-folder 237/6)
  - 44-900 to 44-950, 1941 August-October (Box-folder 237/7)
  - 44-951 to 44-999, 1941 July-October (Box-folder 238/1)
  - 45-1 to 45-50, 1941 May-October (Box-folder 238/2)
  - 45-51 to 45-99, 1941 September-November (Box-folder 238/3)
  - 45-100 to 45-150, 1941 August-November (Box-folder 238/4)
  - 45-151 to 45-199, 1941 October-November (Box-folder 238/5)
  - 45-200 to 45-250, 1941 November-December (Box-folder 238/6)
  - 45-251 to 45-299, 1941 April-December (Box-folder 238/7)
  - 45-400 to 45-450, 1941 September-December, No 45-300 to 45-399. (Box-folder 238/8)
  - 45-451 to 45-499, 1941 September-December (Box-folder 238B/1)
  - 45-500 to 45-550, 1941 November-1942 January (Box-folder 238B/2)
  - 45-551 to 45-599, 1941 December-1942 January (Box-folder 238B/3)
  - 45-600 to 45-650, 1941 December-1942 January (Box-folder 238B/4)
  - 45-651 to 45-699, 1941 September-1942 January (Box-folder 238B/5)
  - 45-700 to 45-749, 1941 December-1942 February (Box-folder 238B/6)
  - 45-750 to 45-799, 1941 December-1942 February (Box-folder 239/1)
  - 45-800 to 45-849, 1941 December-1942 February (Box-folder 239/2)
  - 45-850 to 45-885, 1942 January-February (Box-folder 239/3)
  - 45-886 to 45-927, 1942 February-March (Box-folder 239/4)
  - 45-928 to 45-949, 1942 January-March (Box-folder 239/5)
  - 45-950 to 45-999, 1940 January-1942 March (Box-folder 239/6)
  - 46-1 to 46-49, 1941 October-1942 March (Box-folder 239B/1)
  - 46-50 to 46-99, 1941 November-1942 March (Box-folder 239B/2)
  - 46-100 to 46-149, 1941 September-1942 March (Box-folder 239B/3)
  - 46-150 to 46-199, 1942 February-March (Box-folder 239B/4)
  - 46-200 to 46-249, 1941 December-1942 April (Box-folder 239B/5)
  - 46-250 to 46-299, 1942 March-April (Box-folder 239B/6)
  - 46-300 to 46-349, 1941 July-1942 April (Box-folder 240/1)
  - 46-350 to 46-399, 1942 March-April (Box-folder 240/2)
  - 46-400 to 46-449, 1942 March-April (Box-folder 240/3)
  - 46-450 to 46-499, 1942 March-May (Box-folder 240/4)
  - 46-500 to 46-549, 1942 March-May (Box-folder 240/5)
  - 46-550 to 46-582, 1942 February-May (Box-folder 240B/1)
  - 46-583 to 46-599, 1942 May (Box-folder 240B/2)
  - 46-600 to 46-649, 1942 April-May (Box-folder 240B/3)
  - 46-650 to 46-699, 1942 April-May (Box-folder 240B/4)
  - 46-700 to 46-749, 1942 April-June (Box-folder 240B/5)
  - 46-750 to 46-799, 1941 October-1942 June (Box-folder 241/1)
  - 46-800 to 46-849, 1942 March-June (Box-folder 241/2)
  - 46-850 to 46-883, 1942 June (Box-folder 241/3)
  - 46-884 to 46-912, 1942 May-June (Box-folder 241/4)
  - 46-913 to 46-949, 1942 May-June (Box-folder 241/5)
  - 46-950 to 46-999, 1942 February-July (Box-folder 241/6)
  - 47-1 to 47-45, 1942 May-July (Box-folder 242/1)
  - 47-46 to 47-50, 1942 June-July (Box-folder 242/2)
  - 47-51 to 47-95, 1942 April-July (Box-folder 242/3)
  - 47-96 to 47-99, 1942 July (Box-folder 242/4)
  - 47-100 to 47-132, 1942 April-July (Box-folder 242/5)
  - 47-133 to 47-150, 1942 June-July (Box-folder 242/6)
  - 47-151 to 47-180, 1942 May-July (Box-folder 242/7)
  - 47-181 to 47-199, 1942 June-July (Box-folder 242/8)
  - 47-200 to 47-231, 1942 May-August (Box-folder 242B/1)
  - 47-232 to 47-250, 1942 May-August (Box-folder 242B/2)
  - 47-251 to 47-276, 1942 March-August (Box-folder 242B/3)
  - 47-277 to 47-299, 1942 July-August (Box-folder 242B/4)
  - 47-300 to 47-327, 1942 July-August (Box-folder 242B/5)
  - 47-328 to 47-350, 1942 June-August (Box-folder 242B/6)
  - 47-351 to 47-389, 1942 May-August (Box-folder 243/1)
  - 47-390 to 47-399, 1942 June-August (Box-folder 243/2)
  - 47-400 to 47-418, 1942 August (Box-folder 243/3)
  - 47-419 to 47-441, 1942 July-September (Box-folder 243/4)
  - 47-456, 47-459, 1942 September (Box-folder 243/5)
  - 48-931, Undated (Box-folder 243/6)
  - 49-770, 1942 February (Box-folder 243/7)
  - 50-315, [1943] September (Box-folder 243/8)
  - 54-1 to 54-25A, 1944 August-1945 February (Box-folder 243/9)
  - 54-26 to 54-35, 1945 February (Box-folder 243/10)
  - 54-36 to 54-60, 1944 November-1945 February (Box-folder 243/11)
  - 54-61 to 54-86, 1944 November-1945 February (Box-folder 243/12)
  - 54-87 to 54-99, 1945 January-February (Box-folder 243B/1)
  - 54-100 to 54-125, 1944 August-1945 February (Box-folder 243B/2)
  - 54-126 to 54-150, 1944 August-1945 February (Box-folder 243B/3)
  - 54-151 to 54-180, 1944 December-1945 February (Box-folder 243B/4)
  - 54-181 to 54-199, 1945 January-March (Box-folder 243B/5)
  - 54-200 to 54-226, 1944 August-1945 March (Box-folder 243B/6)
  - 54-227 to 54-249, 1945 February-March (Box-folder 243B/7)
  - 54-250, 1945 March (Box-folder 244/1)
  - 54-251 to 54-282, 1945 January-March (Box-folder 244/2)
  - 54-283 to 54-299, 1945 January-March (Box-folder 244/3)
  - 54-300 to 54-322, 1945 January-March (Box-folder 244/4)
  - 54-323 to 54-349, 1944 November-1945 March (Box-folder 244/5)
  - 54-350 to 54-377, 1945 February-March (Box-folder 244/6)
  - 54-378 to 54-399, 1945 March (Box-folder 244/7)
  - 54-400 to 54-421, 1945 February-March (Box-folder 244/8)
  - 54-422 to 54-449, 1945 February-April (Box-folder 245/1)
  - 54-450 to 54-482, 1945 January-April (Box-folder 245/2)
  - 54-483 to 54-499, 1945 February-April (Box-folder 245/3)
  - 54-500 to 54-531, 1944 August-1945 May (Box-folder 245/4)
  - 54-532 to 54-550, 1945 April (Box-folder 245/5)
  - 54-551 to 54-568, 1945 April (Box-folder 245/6)
  - 54-569 to 54-599, 1945 February-April (Box-folder 245/7)
  - 54-600 to 54-634, 1945 January-April (Box-folder 245/8)
  - 54-635 to 54-648, 1945 March-April (Box-folder 245B/1)
  - 54-650 to 54-679, 1945 January-April (Box-folder 245B/2)
  - 54-680 to 54-699, 1945 April-May (Box-folder 245B/3)
  - 54-700 to 54-724, 1945 April (Box-folder 245B/4)
  - 54-725 to 54-749, 1944 January-1945 May (Box-folder 245B/5)
  - 54-750 to 54-768, 1945 April-May (Box-folder 245B/6)
  - 54-769 to 54-799, 1944 December-1945 May (Box-folder 245B/7)
  - 54-800 to 54-833, 1945 January-May (Box-folder 245B/8)
  - 54-834 to 54-850, 1945 April-May (Box-folder 246/1)
  - 54-851 to 54-885, 1945 April-May (Box-folder 246/2)
  - 54-886 to 54-899, 1945 April-May (Box-folder 246/3)
  - 54-900 to 54-930, 1945 March-May (Box-folder 246/4)
  - 54-931 to 54-949, 1945 March-May (Box-folder 246/5)
  - 54-950 to 54-999, 1944 March-1945 May (Box-folder 246/6)
  - 55-1 to 55-35, 1945 April-May (Box-folder 246/7)
  - 55-36 to 55-50, 1945 April-May (Box-folder 246/8)
  - 55-51 to 55-85, 1945 May-June (Box-folder 247/1)
  - 55-86 to 55-99, 1945 May-June (Box-folder 247/2)
  - 55-100 to 55-128, 1945 April-June (Box-folder 247/3)
  - 55-129 to 55-150, 1945 April-June (Box-folder 247/4)
  - 55-151 to 55-181, 1945 April-June (Box-folder 247/5)
  - 55-182 to 55-199, 1945 June (Box-folder 247/6)
  - 55-200 to 55-230, 1945 April-June (Box-folder 247/7)
  - 55-231 to 55-250, 1945 June (Box-folder 247B/1)
  - 55-251 to 55-267, 1945 June (Box-folder 247B/2)
  - 55-268 to 55-299, 1945 June (Box-folder 247B/3)
  - 55-300 to 55-345, 1943 June-1945 July (Box-folder 247B/4)
  - 55-346 to 55-357, 1945 May-July (Box-folder 247B/5)
  - 55-358 to 55-383, 1945 June-July (Box-folder 247B/6)
  - 55-384 to 55-399, 1945 June-July (Box-folder 247B/7)
  - 55-400 to 55-433, 1945 June-July (Box-folder 247B/8)
  - 55-434 to 55-450, 1945 May-July (Box-folder 248/1)
  - 55-451 to 55-480, 1945 March-July (Box-folder 248/2)
  - 55-481 to 55-499, 1945 June-July (Box-folder 248/3)
  - 55-500 to 55-519, 1945 June-July (Box-folder 248/4)
  - 55-520 to 55-550, 1945 June-September (Box-folder 248/5)
  - 55-554 to 55-572, 1945 January-September (Box-folder 248/6)
  - 55-573 to 55-599, 1945 July-August (Box-folder 248/7)
  - 55-600 to 55-620, 1945 July-August (Box-folder 248B/1)
  - 55-621 to 55-650, 1945 June-August (Box-folder 248B/2)
  - 55-651 to 55-676, 1945 July-August (Box-folder 248B/3)
  - 55-677 to 55-699, 1945 July-August (Box-folder 248B/4)
  - 55-700 to 55-740, 1945 July-August (Box-folder 248B/5)
  - 55-741 to 55-750, 1945 August (Box-folder 248B/6)
  - 55-751 to 55-782, 1945 July-August (Box-folder 248B/7)
  - 55-783 to 55-799, 1944 September-1945 August (Box-folder 249/1)
  - 55-800 to 55-835, 1945 August-September (Box-folder 249/2)
  - 55-836 to 55-851, 1945 August (Box-folder 249/3)
  - 55-852 to 55-874, 1945 July-September (Box-folder 249/4)
  - 55-875 to 55-882, 1945 September (Box-folder 249/5)
  - 55-883 to 55-899, 1945 May-September (Box-folder 249/6)
  - 55-900 to 55-937, 1945 August-September (Box-folder 249/7)
  - 55-938 to 55-950, 1945 September (Box-folder 249/8)
  - 55-951 to 55-982, 1944 June-1945 September (Box-folder 249B/1)
  - 55-983 to 55-999, 1945 September (Box-folder 249B/2)
  - 56-1 to 56-38, 1945 May-September (Box-folder 249B/3)
  - 56-39 to 56-72, 1945 July-September (Box-folder 249B/4)
  - 56-73 to 56-99, 1945 April-October (Box-folder 249B/5)
  - 56-100 to 56-133, 1945 July-October (Box-folder 249B/6)
  - 56-134 to 56-151, 1945 October (Box-folder 250/1)
  - 56-152 to 56-178, 1945 September-October (Box-folder 250/2)
  - 56-179 to 56-199, 1945 September-October (Box-folder 250/3)
  - 56-200 to 56-232, 1945 September-October (Box-folder 250/4)
  - 56-233 to 56-250, 1945 August-October (Box-folder 250/5)
  - 56-251 to 56-289, 1945 August-October (Box-folder 250/6)
  - 56-290 to 56-299, 1945 October (Box-folder 250/7)
  - 56-300 to 56-316, 1945 September-October (Box-folder 251/1)
  - 56-317 to 56-343, 1945 August-October (Box-folder 251/2)
  - 56-344 to 56-357, 1945 August-November (Box-folder 251/3)
  - 56-358 to 56-384, 1945 September-November (Box-folder 251/4)
  - 56-385 to 56-399, 1945 October-November (Box-folder 251/5)
  - 56-400 to 56-430, 1945 October-November (Box-folder 251/6)
  - 56-431 to 56-450, 1945 November (Box-folder 251/7)
  - 56-451 to 56-481, 1945 August-November (Box-folder 251B/1)
  - 56-482 to 56-499, 1945 October-1946 April (Box-folder 251B/2)
  - 56-500 to 56-529, 1945 November (Box-folder 251B/3)
  - 56-530 to 56-549, 1945 November (Box-folder 251B/4)
  - 56-550 to 56-580, 1945 October-November (Box-folder 251B/5)
  - 56-581 to 56-599, 1945 November (Box-folder 251B/6)
  - 56-600 to 56-630, 1944 December-1945 December (Box-folder 252/1)
  - 56-631 to 56-650, 1945 November-December (Box-folder 252/2)
  - 56-651 to 56-663, 1945 November-December (Box-folder 252/3)
  - 56-664 to 56-699, 1922 April-1945 December (Box-folder 252/4)
  - 56-700 to 56-729, 1945 October-December (Box-folder 252/5)
  - 56-730 to 56-749, 1945 October-December (Box-folder 252/6)
  - 56-750 to 56-782, 1945 November-1946 February (Box-folder 252/7)
  - 56-783 to 56-799, 1945 November-December (Box-folder 252B/1)
  - 56-800 to 56-814, 1945 December-1946 January (Box-folder 252B/2)
  - 56-815 to 56-816, 1945 December-1946 January (Box-folder 252B/3)
  - 56-817 to 56-850, 1945 December-1946 January (Box-folder 252B/4)
  - 56-851 to 56-878, 1945 November-1946 January (Box-folder 252B/5)
  - 56-879 to 56-899, 1945 October-1946 January (Box-folder 252B/6)
  - 56-900 to 56-949, 1945 November-1946 January (Box-folder 252B/7)
  - 56-950 to 56-981, 1945 December-1946 January (Box-folder 253/1)
  - 56-982 to 56-999, 1946 January (Box-folder 253/2)